You keep yelling that you
are superior to everyone.
You keep crying out.
Well..
This is the fighting field.
Draw your sword and challenge me.
So we will see...
We will see...
...how you learn by bitter experience.
You're not even equal to me.
How could you challenge me?
They'd cut you into a
thousand pieces with my order.
No.
I'm neither afraid of death...
...nor avoid my fate like you do.
Well..
My presence here...
...is the proof.
Well... This dog...
This corpse...
...should be a lesson for you people!
Come on!
Tell your dog to come for me!
I can fight anyone here!
Altuga!
Hristo!
Avenge Lukas!
Osman..
You made my foolish brother your dog!
-I'll throw your bones under his feet!
-We will see.
Alps! Now!
Captivity of Turks is over!
We'll make their lives miserable now!
My alps and I are ready for
any orders, my Shahzade.
-It's time to slaughter those dastards.
-Someone's coming.
We'll butcher whoever stands on our way!
Whoever attempts to enslave
Turks will face death sooner or later!
Let's go help father, brother.
-Let's go!
-Let's go.
Where did they come from?
While Osman made noise here,
...he placed his men among the local people.
Osman... You will never give up.
We're here, my Bey!
We saved the prisoners, my Bey!
Hit the heathens now! Cut off their tongues!
Thank You, my Allah. Thank You.
I won't let anyone but me kill you, Osman.
Allah is the greatest!
Damn it! What's going on?
They're gone! They're all gone!
Nokers, come with me.
Osman Bey secret tents
Easy, girl. You may burn yourself.
You touched the herbs. That's
why this soup tastes so delicious.
Wait, don't burn yourself.
My mother's voice.
It mixes with your voice, Bala.
Why?
Mother, what are you doing?
We can do that. Give me the axe.
We never let the elders work.
Bala Hatun, may Allah be
pleased with you. I can do it myself.
Don't bother.
It won't bother me at all. Give it to me.
How can we provide peace in our
state if our elders and sisters don't rest?
We should support each other.
-May Allah be pleased with you.
-In the name of Allah, the compassionate, the merciful
Why are you so good?
What my aunt told me...
The woman who killed my family.
My enemy... It can't be you.
Damn it..
Meryem..
Do you still have a headache, my daughter?
Maybe my grandmother's herbs would help.
Come on, let me
rub your head a little.
There is no need.
I'll have some rest, then I will be alright.
Alright. Have some rest.
You affect me badly, Bala.
You are harming me and...
..my revenge.
I shouldn't get close to you.
Because of you...
I betrayed my aunt.
This road leads to Kurupinar.
The trees in that area are so
dense that they block the view.
Osman will use the trees as
a shield and escape, Ulugan.
If necessary, I will burn the
whole forest that protects him...
...and pick his bones from the ashes.
But I will not let him escape. Come on.
-Orhan, check and see if they are coming.
-As you order, my Bey.
My Bey, they are not far away.
They are coming in large numbers. It is
clear that Byzantium and Nokers have united.
Why are we leaving, my Bey?
Give the order, let's ambush and kill them all.
Let's take revenge for the martyrs.
Don't act with blind courage.
First, we will take our
measures, then we will attack.
Now, they outnumber us
I will hit them so hard that...
...even Olcaytu
Khan will hear about it.
God willing my Bey.
My Bey, what are you planning?
You will all hear it at the council.
Kanyumaz. -My Bey.
-You go from the north.
We will go from the south.
-As you order, my Bey.
As you order, my Bey.
We will mislead Ulugan.
We will meet at the tribe! Come on!
Your duty was to ensure the security
of the Arena, and what did you do?
Nothing.
And...
Lukas died.
Then why are you still alive?
I have no patience...
...for foolishness and defeat.
Those who make mistakes will die.
You will only...
..serve our revenge.
The revenge we will take from
Osman is growing day by day.
Hristo.
Report Lukas's death with this letter.
Deliver it to the Emperor immediately.
-Yes ma'am.
The great Emperor...
...will want to turn this
place into hell for Lukas.
We will prepare accordingly.
Osman..
...I will corner you in a way you cannot escape.
Altuga...
What do you hear? Tell us.
Osman..
His mind works like a wolf's, Ulugan.
They have split into two.
He wants to weaken us.
He wants to make his tracks disappear.
I will show him what strength is.
Our fight will be fierce, Osman.
Nokers...
Byzantium soldiers.
Even if you set the whole forest on fire...
...or uproot the great trees...
...you will find
Osman's den. Now, go
We are going to the tribe.
We cannot know where Osman will attack. Come on.
Osman Bey Secret Tents
Osman Bey is coming!
Thanks to Allah!
My father is here.
They came here safely, thanks to Allah.
-Peace be upon you!
-Peace be upon you, my Bey.
Were those traitors punished, my Bey?
My brave Alps...
...my fearless sisters.
Thanks to my Allah.
The one who watered these
blessed lands with blood...
...the one who dreamt of
destroying our glorious state...
..and..
...killed my unborn grandchild...
...Byzantine's
Commander Lukas...
...paid for what he did.
He died as he deserved.
Long live Osman Bey!
The lands that shake under
the steps of the Turks...
...the lands we made our
homeland with our blood...
...will now be the grave for those who...
...sent us away with betrayal...
...for those who disrupted our unity.
The swords we sharpened with revenge...
...will strike the enemy's heart...
...like a burning fire.
O, my people!
Know that the whole world...
...expects a new rise from us.
We will see..
...Allah's justice as our guide...
...and bring the order that they trampled on...
..back.
We will teach the world again that
Turks will never give up, never fall!
Allah is the Greatest! Allah is the Greatest!
Osman Bey!
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
I informed everyone that Lukas dog died, my Bey.
These are valiants who are eager
to stand by you in your da'wah.
Thank you, valiants. Long live.
-I want to see all the Beys in my tent.
-As you order, my Bey.
My gazelle-eyed love...
Are you tired, huh?
No, I am alright.
Every day you return home
...peace fills my heart like the sun, Orhan.
That peace...
...shines from your eyes..
...into my heart.
It becomes a star in the dark nights...
...and lights my way.
It carries me...
...and brings me to you, my Holofira.
The heart that was once full of sorrow...
...healed with your love, Orhan.
What will I do if something happens to you?
Thankfully...
I am not alone anymore.
-I will wait for you with our child.
-I know.
Behind me...
...I have people who await my return.
I have you.
No matter what happens...
..I will always return my Holofira. Always.
Now tell me...
...has my baby, my child...
...been a good companion?
Sure it has.
It's a good companion but just like you...
...it does not know how to stay still.
Is that so?
Don't worry...
Gonca is always with me.
Gonca Hatun.
Thank you.
I've heard you always stay with Holofira.
I don't know how we can repay you.
As long as you are here...
...I won't have to worry about my Hatun.
Thank you.
Holofira is my sister.
And your child is my nephew, Orhan Bey.
If I don't protect Holofira
in this tribe, then who will?
Besides..
...I understand her fear...
...and worries better than anyone.
Thank you.
Long live.
Come on Holofira.
May you be in peace where you lie, my baby.
My hatun..
My rosebud
The dastard..
...who killed our baby and
broke our happiness passed away.
May he burn in flames, Alaaddin.
I hope...
...Allah will give him...
...much worse than what he did to us.
God willing.
Don't fill your heart with grief, my dear.
We need to be strong.
My children and nephews will
grow up together, God willing.
God willing, my Alaaddin. God willing.
How could you let Osman escape?
With all those nokers...
All those soldiers...
How could you do that?
How are you to question me?
I'd cut off your poor head.
The arrow is off the bow, Ulugan.
I don't care about my life anymore.
I need blood.
I need vengeance.
Osman's alps and family have been encouraged.
If we turn against each other now.
...Osman will destroy us.
What? Are you afraid, Kayi boy?
Afraid of death?
I'm never afraid of Osman.
This is all because of you, Ilbay.
We relied on your wife's brother.
And we got deceived.
And this red woman's spy as well.
My spy didn't betray.
This is my final talk to you.
If you make another mistake
...your heads won't stay over your shoulders.
Find Osman immediately.
Otherwise, I'll bury you
three in the same grave.
You have to tell me where
your master hides, brother.
You have to tell. Come on.
Leave my father, dastard!
What kind of brother are you?
Where is Osman, brother?
Tell me where Osman is.
Speak! I don't want to kill you
in front of your son. Come on!
I won't speak even if you skin me.
Lukas today.
Ulugan tomorrow.
The circle tightens, Altuga.
Osman will be the hell for the cruel!
Whoever stands beside the dog called Ulugan...
...will burn to ashes one by one.
And you..
Look.
Brother.
You have time until tomorrow.
-Otherwise...
-Otherwise?
Otherwise?
You can't scare me with death.
Come on, kill me.
To serve a vile dog
..kill me.
That would suit you.
Ghazi.
Make your father come around.
Make him speak.
Otherwise I will cut off
both of your heads tomorrow.
I swear on the spirit of my almighty father...
...that I will do it.
Ghazi.
Ghazi... Ghazi.
Father, father.
Go away, dastards! Dogs!
-Dastards.
-Father, are you alright?
-I'm fine, boy. I'm fine.
-Father.
I'm fine.
Many traitors once among us...
...and many enemies got united against us.
But the one in the right path...
...has always become victorious.
-Thank Allah, my Bey.
-Thanks to Allah, my Bey.
Now we know what to do.
We'll clear the dark clouds over our state.
The weapons we took from Mongolians.
The alps Yusuf Bey sent for us.
They will be the key of the lock
they built against Kayi's freedom.
For sure, we have both
alps and weapons, my Bey.
But I don't know if that's
enough to attack the tribe.
No.
We won't attack the tribe
as the heathens expect.
We'll capture Sogut.
You say the wildfire of Kayi
will burn in Kayi first, huh?
It will be so.
You say the enemy expect us
to attack the tribe, huh, my Bey?
What's the plan, father?
How will we distract the dog called Ulugan?
You and Orhan will split up and...
...attack the spot where
Mongolians stay near the tribe.
So Ulugan and his dogs will
think our next target is the tribe...
...and take defense formation.
Maybe, they'll never get out of there?
-God willing.
God willing, son.
Boran, alps and I will try to
open the smallest of the tunnels...
...leading to Sogut which we sealed earlier.
In the meantime, you'll
have finished your duty, sons.
As you order, my Bey.
Everybody knows their duties.
Here we go.
Fatma Hatun.
Meryem.
Hatuns made sherbet.
It feels good to drink before sleep.
-Well thought.
We can drink together.
What's the matter, Bala?
What are you thinking about?
Lukas is dead now.
They'll get more furious and attack, my Bey.
No.
It's good that the vile dog is dead.
Our people got encouraged and confident.
People and alps never lost
their trust in you, my Bey.
You did everything for them.
Everyone, from the eldest to babies, knows this.
Yes. You're right. Well...
Were you never afraid that we would fail?
No. Why would I be?
You don't know what being
Osman Bey's wife means.
What does it mean? Let me know.
It's such a thing...
...that neither disasters
nor enemies can scare me.
I know this.
If Osman the Brunette says he'll come.
...he will come to his Bala no matter what.
He comes for help wherever
he is and whatever he's doing.
He'll never me, his sons or his state.
-What a man Osman the Brunette is!
-Yes.
You should see Osman the
Brunette from my eyes just for once.
Bala.
Bala, stop. I'm here. Why are you doing this?
I just hurt my feet. I didn't fall weak.
This is not my first time.
Come here. Come to me.
Come here, over here.
You should see yourself from my eyes, in fact.
What am I like?
Come closer.
Come closer to me.
You..
You're the mountain I'm leaning on.
You're my harbor in my hard times.
My moon.
My day and night.
You are my heart.
You were always with me. Always.
When I swung swords and fought the heathens.
...I always had you in my mind.
Oh my strong wife...
Since the day you said yes
to me, you have suffered a lot.
Your tears have never stop running down.
Compared to your sufferings,
mine means nothing, Osman.
I vowed to be with you.
As long as you are with
me, I'm ready for anything.
Just be with me.
Your absence burns me like fire.
It burns me to ashes, Osman.
-Oh...
Speaking of the ashes, stop there.
You should know the ashes inside me.
You are my accepted prayer.
All my burdens get lighter with you.
May Allah never let me see your absence.
May He never let me see your absence.
Yours either, my Osman.
Yours either.
Come on, father. We'll get out of here.
Come on.
Of course we'll get out, son.
Remember.
Cerkutay never dies.
Don't confuse your mind, Cerkutay.
It's impossible for your to escape.
Ghazi, stay behind me.
Escape?
This place won't be your
home but only your grave.
I'll take your hopes...
...out of your unbreakable souls!
You won't find peace even for a single day.
Your son Ghazi will remember you as a traitor.
He'll be raised as a Mongolian.
Nokers, take Ghazi.
Father! Get off!
-Ghazi!
Ghazi! Ghazi! I'll kill you!
I swear I'll kill you! I swear I will kill you!
With your death, I will wipe out the shame...
...you put on us with your betrayal, Cerkutay.
Father! Father! No!
No!
Don't die! Dont' die!
No! No!
Father! Father!
Father!
Die, you dastard!
No! No!
Ghazi..
Father... -Ghazi..
I seek forgiveness in Allah!
Please, my Allah...
Please, help, my Allah...
Please my Allah...
Take from my life and
give it to them, my Allah...
Take from my years...
My Allah, do not test me with their absence...
Send word to Sofia.
I need to talk to her. -From Sofia.
Poena, I knew you would come here.
I still don't know how Osman found
out we were going to attack, but...
...I am sure you did not do this. You are...
...not a person who would protect
the ones who killed your family...
...you would not betray your parents.
Right, Poena?
You would never let your family down, right?
My little bird...
Don't you ever fool me.
When the sun rises...
...bring Bala to the riverside. I trust you.
You trust me aunt.
But I betrayed you.
I betrayed my family...
..you..
...and my revenge.
But I had to.
I owed them a life.
When the sun rises, bring Bala to the riverside.
I trust you.
They stay close to the entrance of the tunnel.
These are patrol nokers, my Bey.
Let's wait for them to leave.
If they hear the noise,
more will come from around.
No.
We need to open the tunnel before Orhan arrives.
We will attack them suddenly and kill them all.
As you order, my Bey.
Alps.
Now. Walk!
Let alone a single inch
of this land, even the preys of...
...these lands are forbidden
for you, you infidel dogs.
Remove their corpses.
Otherwise, they will realize
that we are sneaking into the city.
Alps, the duty is yours.
Light the torches.
Give it to me.
My Bey...
When we were closing the
passages leading to Sogut...
...we used quite a lot of flying flames.
My concern is that...
...despite all this effort...
...what if we can't reach the
end of the passage my Bey?
What will we do then? -No.
No Boran. We will. We need to open it.
My Bey, we will not give
up. We will open it. But...
The tunnel is quite long. And also,
it's closed off at every point, my Bey.
-Did you give up hope, Boran?
-I would never, my Bey.
Do you think it's easy for the state to revive
and for the nation to regain its freedom?
If necessary, we will dig
here until our picks break...
...and if necessary, until our nails are
pulled out and the skin of our hands is torn.
We must take Sogut. You
will never fall into despair.
Okay, my Bey.
For sure, for sure We will take it.
We will dig.
Come on now.
Come on.
Let's start digging!
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
Here, brother. My Allah, let us defeat them.
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
What did you do to..
...my tribe, my people...
...my children?!
You infidels!
What did you want from them?
What did they do to you?
What did they do?
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
-Is everyone ready?
-Yes my Shahzade.
Our Alps are waiting for your
orders to send these dogs to hell.
Okay.
They are so confident in themselves that
death will catch them before they even notice.
The area around the headquarters.
It's surrounded by traps.
These dogs' confidence comes from there.
Are there traps? Where?
Between the guards.
They are walking a longer
path to avoid stepping on it.
From where will we attack?
We will attack the guards.
Are you ready Ekrem Bey?
Turks are always ready
for a battle, my Shahzade.
-Sure. Aykurt.
-My Shahzade.
Give them the sign.
Trap!
The Righteous!
Come on! Come on!
Allah is the Greatest!
Ulugan will lose his mind
when he hears about the raid.
Anyone who fights against Osman
Bey will never find peace, brother.
Now, he will take precautions
at the tribe out of fear.
And with Allah's permission,
we will take Sogut, God willing.
God willing.
Now, gather the weapons
and set the headquarters on fire.
Nothing belonging to these
dogs will remain in this land.
As you order my Shahzade. Come on.
Mongol Headquarters
Come on!
There is a lot to do! Hurry!
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
Trap!
The wolf has arrived.
The jackal's reign is over.
Now it is time to pay the price!
Ya Allah!
Protect the prisoners!
Allah is the Greatest!
Destroy this place! Don't let anyone escape!
Allah is Eternal!
This rock... It carries all the
load that blocks the passage.
If we remove it, our path will open.
God willing my Bey, God willing.
Boran...
It doesn't seem like it will work.
It does not seem like it will move.
Forget it. We will keep digging.
Look, you're very tired.
Take a rest for a while.
Yes, my Bey.
Alps!
Come on, it's your turn now.
Stop, stop brother.
Stop.
My Allah, give me strength.
Make me dust under my Bey's feet..
...but give me the power to open this tunnel.
In the name of Allah.
Come on.
Allah.
Move!
Is there any trace, Altuga?
From sunrise to sunset...
...we rode our horses all
night. Commander Ulugan.
We didn't see any smoke or fire.
We found no trace of Osman.
Go, don't come back to me until you find Osman.
No food, no water.
You won't even sleep!
Get lost!
Red Hatun.
Ilbay and his wife. You will
search for Osman everywhere.
You wanted revenge go and take it!
I work alone, Ulugan.
I don't want to carry a burden with me.
Sofia, don't think I am like others.
I have no friends.
And my enemy does not live either.
Stop fighting like dogs among yourselves.
If you can't find Osman,
you better get ready to die.
Ah Ulugan.
If you can't find Osman, how
will you answer to Olcaytu?
Ilbay, this devil will do something.
She is a devil after all.
Anything can come from her.
What's the situation?
I will remove this rock from its place.
I will open the path to Sogut, with
Allah's permission. I will open it.
Boran!
Leave it.
Leave it. Get out of there.
I will open it, my Bey.
Don't worry. I will open it.
Boran!
Don't you hear me?
Ya Allah
Boran
Boran! Boran! Boran
Boran. Hang on, my valiant.
Boran
Osman Bey Secret Tents
What am I going to do?
I came to you with a heart
as hard as stone, Bala.
But you are melting my heart.
I won't allow this.
Bring the torch!
Come on! Faster! Hurry!
Hold it here! Hold it here!
Ah, you didn't listen to me!
You didn't listen to me, Boran!
You didn't listen to me!
Come on valiants, hurry! Hurry!
My Allah..
His hand... His hand.
Come on! Hurry!
Hang on... Boran
Boran!
My valiant...
He is not breathing. He is
not breathing. Boran. Boran!
Wake up! Come on my valiant!
Open your eyes! Don't! Come on!
Give him water. Water! Boran.
Come on! Come on! -Here, my Bey.
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Come on my valiant.
Come on!
Boran!
Look at me.
Are you alright?
I am alright, my Bey. Thank Allah.
-Come here.
My Bey. My Bey.
I have opened the path to Sogut, Thank Allah.
You've opened it. And
you've opened it like a lion.
Come on. Come on, Alps. Help.
Get up, come on!
Ulgen, are you alright?
You've been thoughtful since the salaat(prayer).
I had terrible nightmares, Bala.
I didn't know what to do.
What did you see, Ulgen?
My Cerkutay and Ghazi...
..died.
Altuga killed them with no mercy.
May Allah forbid that, Ulgen.
Dreams don't come true.
Don't think of bad things.
As long as Ghazi is with Cerkutay
Bey, they will be fine. Don't worry.
Your nightmares will end, Ulgen.
We will come back all
together with Allah's will.
And go back to our tribe, God willing.
God willing.
Just think... What would Ghazi
say if he saw you upset like this?
Because of the spy among us,
...nobody except Beys and Shahzades will go out.
No, it's not.
But she always gets lost.
Mother, did you say something?
No, girl. I said nothing.
Where are you going, mother?
I'll go look around, dear. You go on.
Mother, you shouldn't go
alone. Shall I come with you?
I won't go far away dear. You go on.
Come, Bala. Come.
The vengeance shall be ended.
Follow me silently.
Where are you going without informing, Meryem?
You always disappear
What are you trying to do, Meryem?
You came this long way to pick up herbs?
I'm afraid. For the first time, I'm so scared.
Why?
You can't be the one to protect those who
killed your family and betray your parents.
Why, Bala?
Why didn't you give my family
affection that you give to everyone?
Why are you forcing me to take my vengeance?
Why?
What are they doing?
Why are they torturing innocent people?
You disbelievers!
What are they doing?
It's forbidden to perform the salaat(prayer)!
You have to serve Ulugan now!
You will definitely pay for this torture!
Shut up or I'll kill you!
Tyrants!
Murderers!
Help us.
Show mercy for us, my Allah.
-Old man.
-My Bey.
Old man.
Just stop, stop. Stop, old man.
Be quiet. Nokers shouldn't hear us.
We all pray for salvation, my Bey.
We're too weak to resist
against those evil Mongolians.
Old man.
You have to stay strong. We need that.
They tortured us terribly, my Bey.
Elders, children and woman are miserable.
They took down our flag and silenced the azan.
Look, old man.
Even if they take down our flag.
Even if they silence the
azan of Muhammad (PBUH),
...we will always keep mentioning Allah.
They will see and know...
...that neither our flag will come
down nor our azan will be silenced.
Nor they can enslave Turks.
Don't be worrying.
May Allah give you a long life, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you. Aameen.
Son, come here.
-Thank you. You've come on time.
-You're welcome, my Bey.
-Come here, son.
-Alright.
What's the situation near the tribe?
My Bey, we made such noise
...Ulugan will go mad when he hears about it.
He must be thinking about what
direction we'll attack from now.
Thank you, thank you.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, my Bey. -Thank you, my Bey.
My Bey, if you let me, I want to
be the one to raise our flag in Sogut.
I'd ready to sacrifice
my life to have this honor.
Alright. Alright.
You're right.
For your father Bayhan Bey and
those warriors who fought for the state
...you should do this and remember them.
Well..
After the big noise,
...everything will be exposed.
But until that time, we will act silently.
Here we go, warriors.
Did you find Osman, Altuga?
No, Commander Ulugan.
Why are you here then?
Do you have a death wish?
While looking for Osman, I heard that the
camps and outposts near the tribe got raided.
They killed all the nokers.
This is Osman's doing.
What are you saying, Altuga?
It seems Osman is going to attack the tribe.
He wants to break our strength.
No. Even if you fools believe that,
..I don't.
If Osman were to attack the tribe,
he wouldn't have made such noise.
Although Osman is our enemy
...he is a smart warrior.
He'll attack right into our heart.
In this case, what is Osman going to do, Ulugan?
He wants to distract us.
He is acting wisely.
But I won't be deceived.
He's going to attack Sogut, obviously.
Get prepared. We're going to Sogut.
Bala Hatun, we've gone
too far. You aren't safe here.
She's going towards the stream.
Where is she going?
Damn it.
Where did this ache come from?
Meryem.
-Bala Hatun.
-Girl, what are you doing here?
Are you alright? Were you crying?
I always have headache.
So I came to the riverbank
to pick up some herbs.
Oh my dear.
You should have told Shahzade Alaaddin.
He would have found some cure for you.
He prepared a cure but it didn't work.
You said herbs grow up in the riverbank.
-So I came here.
-My beautiful girl...
Does it hurt you so much?
We're too far away.
Why did you follow me, Bala
Hatun? We should go back.
No, dear. We are already here now.
Let's find the herbs and heal you. Come on.
Bala!
Sofia.
Did you follow my smell, dog?
I didn't believe when my
soldiers said they saw you.
You came to me with your own feet, huh?
Come on.
Don't waste my time.
Surrender, Bala.
Don't you know me at all, Sofia?
I know you more than you know yourself, Bala.
You did it, little bird. Come to your aunt now.
Bala!
Surrender.
Or I'll kill this
..little demon.
You snake! Leave the girl.
This is because of me,
Bala Hatun. Because of me.
It's not your fault, dear.
That snake always hides behind someone!
This is the difference
between you and me, Sofia.
You are a coward.
Smart move, Bala.
But this is the end for you.
Oh... You got a big prey, Sofia.
But she is ours now.
She is mine!
Not yours, Sofia. We are together now.
Ulugan will be happy to hear this.
Traitors! You betrayers!
Nokers, take both of them.
Right, Sofia. You caught her for Ulugan.
Of course.
Easy.
It's time to pay, Bala.
We're going to my tribe.
I will make you pay there.
Keep playing your game for now, Begum.
It won't take long.
No. Osman can't do anything
to us as long as we have you.
My era has begun.
Move.
Where is my mother?
-We can't find her.
-Bala is gone!
I looked everywhere but couldn't find her.
Sisters haven't seen him either.
If she had gone to father, we would know.
It must be something else.
Meryem isn't around either.
Something happened for sure!
Don't worry, Fatma. We'll find
Mother Bala. Alps, prepare the horses!
Holofira, we can go look
for her. You stay in the tribe.
-You're carrying a baby. You should be careful.
-No, Gonca.
If I stay, it will eat my heart
out. We should look together.
Besides, you are with me.
I will be alright. Don't worry.
-Fine.
-Ulgen.
You stay in the tribe and keep
security with Sisters, alright?
You're in charge here.
Remove these.
They will notice us soon.
With the noise that the
people of Sogut will hear...
...everyone will come to the square, my Bey.
-Yes, yes.
Come on. It is time to hunt.
Take these. Come on!
Come on.
Aykurt, set the flying flames.
You will carry them inside, come on!
Come on.
We will turn this place into a bloodbath today.
For every drop of tears they shed....
...we will take our revenge by
shedding their blood, my Bey.
God willing, son, God willing.
Our work isn't done yet.
We are just beginning. Let's go.
Osman.
My Bey.
The upstairs is clean.
Okay.
Now we know what they have been hiding.
Nokers! Osman is here!
They've entered the inn! Attack! Come on!
Come on!
My Bey, flying flames..
The flying flames on our backs were
enough to destroy all the Mongols.
Now imagine what will happen with these, son.
-They surrounded the inn, my Bey.
-This is what I wanted.
Let them come, let them come.
Everyone knows what to do. Let's go.
Come on!
Osman!
I will drown you in your own blood.
Blood, blood, blood!
Trap!
The sounds come from Sogut, Ulugan.
Osman must have attacked already!
Hurry, let's go!
Alps, we will search the
area thoroughly, come on!
Aunt, these are our Alps!
Mongols did this. It's their arrow.
Alps, be cautious, they were ambushed.
This..
...is my mother's.
This belongs to my mother, aunt.
If we look at the tracks..
...my mother fought with them.
But since she is not here...
If she could have escaped,
she would have come to the tribe.
Apparently, they have my mother.
My mother must be their prisoner now.
Meryem might be with her.
Then we need to inform
my father immediately. Alps!
Bury the martyrs, we are
going to Sogut. Let's go.
Let's go.
Come on Alps!
-Let go! Don't touch!
-Bala Hatun!
Let go
Kayi's people!
If you want to see the end
of pride, look at Bala Hatun.
Learn a lesson, look at what happened to her...
...who once proudly walked around the tribe.
Do you think we are defeated
because our hands are chained, Begum?
What is a title, what is glory?
We give our lives for our da'wah
and we are honored by that.
But you..
For the power, you trample on your
honor and become the lowest of the low.
Is there a better example than you?
You and your Bey are the same, Bala.
You love telling the story of your
defeat as if it's a victory, right?
But you are disgraced.
There is no way out for you now.
Sofia is right.
You are defeated Bala.
Now you will kneel before
me in front of your people!
We lost martyrs, we fell as martyrs.
But we never knelt, Begum.
We drowned the oppression of
the tyrants and protected our da'wah.
And this will never change!
Now shut up and obey!
Kneel
Hold her tightly!
Let go! Begum! I will kill you as well
I will kill all of you!
Let go!
Let go! Don't touch!
My word and my wife Begum
Hatun's word are the only decree.
One who does not kneel
before us will surely die!
Pull yourselves together!
-You traitor!
O glorious people of
Kayi, we will get over this!
We will take our tribe back from these dastards.
The end of those who work with the
infidels and tyrants is torment, Begum!
Torment! Let go! Don't touch!
Enough!
Take them to the caged tent!
O people! Stand tall!
Never give up hope
Even if we fall, we will never be defeated!
Allah is the Greatest!
I wish I could kill her right now.
We cannot punish Bala before Ulugan arrives.
Where is Ulugan, Sofia?
-In Sogut.
Osman planned a big game to take Sogut back.
Ulugan is dealing with him.
If Osman takes Sogut, it will be more
difficult for us to stand against him.
Osman can do anything for Bala.
Bala is the biggest advantage we have.
Now, the dogs have captured Bala Hatun.
First us...
...now Bala Hatun.
Father? Father, are you alright?
Father, are you alright?
-I am, my lion.
I am.
Father...
...we need to do something.
Besides..
...the time my uncle...
...Altuga gave is running out.
We will handle it.
But no matter what...
...we won't tell them where Osman Bey is.
We won't tell them where Osman Bey is.
I won't let them hurt you.
Even if I die..
...I will let you come
together with your mother.
No.
That will not happen Cerkutay Bey.
I spent my entire childhood without you.
Besides, you will organize my wedding.
I will. I will.
My Bey made sure these wooden
railings were strong back then.
Everything my Bey does, he does it perfectly.
I wish they were weaker.
We could break them down and leave!
You, Ghazi...
You are making me laugh even in this situation.
We will get out of here, my lion.
We will..
God willing.
Slowly!
Here.
Dastards!
Get in there!
One by one, you are falling into our hands.
Next to you...
...we are keeping traitor
Cerkutay and his puppy.
Come on.
Ghazi..
He is too young. It's all my fault...
Why did you leave before letting us know?
Didn't I tell you that you
won't go anywhere alone?
That's why. Because it was dangerous...
...I was going to leave
silently and collect the herbs.
If I told you..
...you would not allow me
and you would come with me.
Yes!
We would not leave you alone, but...
-Look, it's worse now.
Forgive me, Bala Hatun.
Anyway.
There must be something
good in this, my daughter.
What might be good right now?
"You may dislike something
although it is good for you...
...or like something although it is bad for you
God knows and you do not"
Surah Al Baqarah 216
It's time now! Revenge!
It's the day of war! Come
on! Attack, people of Sogut!
Allah is the Greatest!
Do not show mercy to anyone, Alps! Don't!
Come on Alps!
Allah is the Greatest!
We'll sacrifice our lives
for our state! Allah-u Akbar!
As long as a state have such a nation
..it will never fall!
Allah is the greatest!
Come on, brothers!
Saruca!
Raise our glorious banner.
Hold on, banner. We are almost there.
You will wave where you belong.
Allah is the greatest!
Nokers, let's water Sogut
with the blood of Kayi!
Hearing that you are a prisoner,
...Osman Bey won't stop, right?
What if he surrenders?
I won't let that happen.
We'll get out of here, Meryem.
How?
They think they are the predators
and we are the preys, huh?
But as the deer knows the
mountain, the hunter will be hunted.
This is our tribe, my girl.
We'll get out of here.
Bala.
I hope you don't feel uncomfortable.
You vile dog.
Why would I feel uncomfortable?
This is my tribe.
I will send you where you deserve, Begum.
You can't overpower me, Bala.
Look. Your people, tent
and tribe... They are all mine.
And you are my prisoner.
Come closer. Are you afraid?
You say this is your tribe.
Your wound is in so deep, right, Begum?
My tribe, my tent and people...
I will take all of them back.
But there is something you can't take from me.
What is it?
You'll never be able to take my
husband, my love and my place, Begum.
Ever.
Are you angry, Begum?
This slap is not for you but for the
cruelty you showed against my people.
Filthy woman! Come on,
Meryem. Let's find Cerkutay.
My boy.
-Father.
My brave boy.
I'm very hungry.
Starving
As hungry as a wolf.
Bala Hatun.
Bala... Bala Hatun.
-Ghazi.
We'll be saved.
Close the door.
Close the door, girl.
Bala Hatun.
-Are you alright?
-We're good.
We have to get out of
here quickly. Let's get out.
They may notice any moment.
-Come on, Ghazi.
-Ghazi, stick to Meryem.
Ghazi. Cerkutay.
Let's go.
Nokers, catch her! She's running off!
Run and never look behind!
-Meryem, take this. Run! Run!
-Come on.
Don't let them escape!
Catch them, come on!
Come here, dastards.
Whoever did this to my homeland
I will cut off their arms and legs!
-We'll break them all, brother!
-For sure, brother!
For sure!
We'll make all of them regret
that they came to the frontiers!
Ya Allah!
Come on, brothers! Come on!
We'll eradicate these dogs! Come on!
Thank you, my Bey!
Saruca
Boran Bey, protect Saruca!
Even if you break my arms and
wings... Even if you take out my heart.
...this flag will wave!
Saruca.
Praise be, my warrior. Praise be.
Allah is the greatest!
Ulugan, forgive me but...
Why are we glad as if we were victorious?
Why don't we fight?
-They...
...are fighting in vain, Altuga.
A gazelle's struggle in a hyena's paw.
Osman just shaved my beard by capturing Sogut.
But I will cut off his head.
We're losing Sogut, Ulugan.
When Olcaytu hears this...
Shut up, Altuga.
You don't see the future.
I'm holding Osman's heart in my hand.
As long as I have his tribe
...he'll fall into my trap sooner
or later and beg me like a dog.
Then we will be victorious.
We'll be victorious.
You can't go anywhere, Bala.
Come on, people!
Horses are here, Bala Hatun.
Alaca is here too. Come on!
-Let's go.
My Alaca.
-Ilbay, do something. They're escaping.
-Bring the horses!
Let's go.
We won't let you catch Bala!
I will come back and take
our tribe back. Don't worry!
Come on! Come on!
People!
You are betraying your kin!
If you stand against me,
...I will kill everyone
including women and children!
I swear!
Come on.
There is no god but Allah.
Old man, don't do this.
Don't embarrass me. Please.
May Allah be pleased with you, my Bey.
You didn't let us be slaves for the enemy.
May Allah give you such a gift...
...that your name will
spread all around the world.
That your generations will prevail.
That your children will have reputation
and keep the order in the world.
Old man, don't.
I don't seek praise here.
I don't want that.
I just intend to spread Allah's religion.
And provide peace and order here.
My boy, the brave should be praised.
May Allah be very pleased with you.
Thank you.
My Beys.
My alps.
I took vengeance and kept my promise.
I never abandoned the
right path for my comfort...
...or bowed against cowards,
dastards and betrayers!
I never sold our freedom for coins!
Now... I swear on this smoke...
...that we will never give up
fighting as long as I keep breathing
-We will never give up!
-Allah is the greatest!
Allah-u Akbar!
Father!
Father.
My daughter...
-Father! My mother...
What happened to your mother?
They abducted my mother, father.
Nokers took my mother away!
How?
What?
How? How?
We don't know how, father.
But we followed their tracks.
They led us to the tribe.
Bring my horse here!
-Alps! Hurry! Now!
You stay here.
Close the doors.
My sons.
Come on.
Ya Allah..
Come on!
Bala Hatun.
-Bala Hatun. Bala Hatun.
-Cerkutay.
You take Ghazi and Meryem. And leave.
I will waste their time.
No. No. We will go together.
-Bala Hatun.
This is the best way.
Run and survive.
Good.
Come on Ghazi. Come on my lion. Go to Bala.
-Come on. May Allah help you.
-You too, Cerkutay.
Be careful.
Come on! Come on Alaca!
Show us how fast you are!
Let's go!
Bala Hatun.
Come on!
I know a way! Come with me! This way!
Come with me!
We found them! Come on!
This way! Come on! -Begum Hatun!
Come on. -You go.
I will go there from behind.
Come on
I will not fall for the game you are playing.
You will die today Bala. Come on!
My Allah, do not test me with my love...
Come on!
Bala Hatun!
Bala Hatun are you alright?
-I am alright, Ghazi.
I am alright. Come on!
Bala Hatun!
Are you alright? -I am alright.
Dastards...
Be careful Bala Hatun.
Ghazi. Go with your Meryem sister.
-Come on, Meryem, get off the horse.
-No, Bala Hatun.
-No, I won't leave you alone.
-Ghazi..
Go and save yourself. She wants me.
Come on, my son. Come on!
Run now! Go!
Go!
Hurry!
You don't have any breath left to take!
Don't run away! Come here, Bala!
Come on Iltutan! Come on! Bala!
I am coming, Bala!
I am coming Bala!
Come on, my girl
Come on.
Stop.
Come, my Alaca. Come.
Look everywhere, don't let her escape!
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Bala..
Come.
Neither Ulugan, nor Osman.
I won't wait for anyone.
You will die today, Bala.
Begum..
Move!
I said move!
So that you love Bala so much...
...then you must die as well
Alaca! My Alaca!
Don't worry Bala...
You don't need a horse anymore.
-Begum...
I will kill you Begum. I will kill you!
Come on Meryem! Come on!
We must find Bala Hatun! Come on!
-Ghazi! Ghazi!
Ghazi, what are you doing?
Bala Hatun let them chase her for us!
Where are you going?
That's better! Bala Hatun
risked her own life for us!
Now it's our turn Meryem!
We must find her!
What can you even do to them, Ghazi?
Anything for Bala Hatun!
Come on Meryem! We must go there!
Come on!
Make your decision, Meryem.
You will either come with me or stay here!
Damn it!
I swear, I will kill you Begum!
You will pay for your betrayal!
I became a traitor because of you!
If you hadn't come, Osman...
Don't you say my husband's name again!
You are...
...a traitor who betrayed her state!
You are a traitor...
...who betrayed her brother!
You cannot defeat me Bala!
This fire will kill you, Bala.
I ripped out your heart, Osman. Now it's over.
Your Bala is gone.
-We could not find her. -I did.
I, Begum Hatun, took my revenge.
I punished the woman who disgraced
me and sent me away from my tribe.
I killed Bala.
No..
No...
I will save Bala Hatun!
No Ghazi. Ghazi, no.
They will catch us!
We cannot do anything to them!
You are right.
We cannot do anything.
We cannot do anything, Meryem.
But my father can.
My father can, Meryem. I
will go and find my father!
Ghazi, no.
Ghazi stop!
Alaca..
Mother!
Alaca, what happened to you?
Bala...
Where are you, mother?
My Bey, the bloodstains of Alaca lead this way.
Come on Alps!
Come on!
Traitor! Begum!
Begum!
May this fire grow even stronger, Bala.
Stay here, and make sure
that Bala turns into ashes.
My Allah..
My Allah, help me!
Osman!
My children!
Come on.
I bear witness that there
is no god but Allah... Ozgtir.
...and I bear witness that
Muhammad is the Messenger of Allah.
It's over, Bala.
It's over.
You're dead.
And it's over.
If it's over,
...why does it hurt me so much?
Osman Bey! My Bey! Help, my Bey!
-Osman Bey.
-Ghazi.
-What's going on?
What happened?
-What?
-Bala Hatun is burning in the cabin, my Bey!
What are you talking about? Where?
In the cabin ahead, my Bey.
-Bala...
-Help, my Bey. Bala Hatun is burning
-Alps!
-Let's go.
Come on!
Bala? Where is Bala?
-No.
-Wait, my Bey!
Bala?
Bala! No! Bala!
No! This can’t happen!
-Mother!
-Leave me!
-Leave me! Mother!
-My Shahzade!
Mother!
-What is this?
-Leave me!
-My Shahzade.
-Leave me! Mother!
-Mother!
-What is this, my Allah?
Bala. Don't worry. Don't worry.
This can't be happening.
No. No.
Leave me! Leave me! Mother!
I said leave me!
This can't be happening.
No.
This isn't real.
Bala!
No!
Leave me! My mother is in those flames!
-My Shahzade.
-Leave me! Mother!
What have they done to us?
What have they done, Bala?
What have those heathens done?
What have you done?
You heathens!
Mother!
Now this fire will be my fire.
These flames will be my flames.
Mother! Leave me!
-My Shahzade.
-Mother!
Bala.
Fire in every ash of yours..
...will become your flames one by one.
From now on, death is forbidden for me
and life is forbidden for you!